# **Professional Summary**

Engaged, team player, creative professional with more than 7 years' experience as a Systems Analyst and Project Manager, plus 2 years' experience in Customer Service. Seeking to leverage exemplary leadership, analytical, coding and customer service skills.

# **Work History**

### **Research Assistant**

03/2010 to present

UNSW- Sydney, Australia

Helping the research team in improving the quality of the database where data is being used to researches. Importing new data received from different partners, cleansing them and transferring into our database model.

· Managing 3 databases and more than 200.000 patients' data stored.

**Teacher** 02/2018 to 02/2019

Sydney Language Solutions- Sydney, Australia

Teaching the Portuguese language to students from all ages and different nationalities.

Night Manager

02/2018 to 01/2019

Meriton Suites- Sydney, Australia

Managing the operations of the 179 rooms onsite available, auditing, managing and training staff, guest accounting, greeting and welcoming guests, complaint handling and resolution, attending to guest enquiries, requests and following up if required.

**Developer** 06/2017 to 03/2019

**Home Informatica-** Sao Paulo, Brazil (Home Office from Sydney)

Working as programmer developing systems to companies, creating and modifying computer programs, maintaining historical records by documenting program development, maintaining professional and technical knowledge by attending educational workshops, and establishing personal networks;

Night Manager

08/2017 to 01/2018

Backpackers HQ - Sydney, Australia

Managing the operations of the hostel, ensuring all guests abide by hostel rules, high levels of customer service are maintained and also that the hostel identifies and meets the changing needs of guests.

Systems Analyst & Project Manager

09/2011 to 06/2017

Itau Unibanco (Brazilian International Bank)- Sao Paulo, Brazil

I worked in a plethora of IT projects, participating at all stages of the Development Life Cycle: planning, creating, testing, deploying and doing maintenance of systems. Most of the time, working with Mainframe Environment. Planning and executing updates in the system. Working in a system that covers over a billion number of data every day. Also worked with web development.

Acting as Project Manager, leading teams from 5 to 8 developers including professional of different areas in projects of different sizes.

- · Recognized every year with "exceed expectations" by the managers.
- The only Junior Analyst of the original team promoted in the second year.

#### Front runner

12/2009 to 03/2010

McDonald's - Rawlins, United States of America

Greeting guests, taking orders personally and by headset, taking care of the work environment.

· First real-life English experience, elected "the smile of the year".

### **Education**

Master of Information and Communication Technology Western Sydney University - Sydney

present- 2020

MBA in Information Technology

University of Sao Paulo - USP - Brazil

2016

**Bachelor** in Medical Informatics

University of Sao Paulo - USP - Brazil

2011

Certifications

**Project Manager Professional** - 2017, PMI

Scrum Fundamentals - 2018, SCRUMstudy

# **Skills**

**Programming** Cobol, Java, JCL, C, C++, HTML, PHP and SQL. With notions of Python, R, MatLab, Swift, Objective-C, C#, .Net, JavaScript and CSS.

**Database** Microsoft SQL Server, msSQL MySQL, PostgreSQL.

**Software** MS Office Suite (Access, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Project), Photoshop.

**Systems** Linux, Windows and Macintosh OS X.